const TRIVIA = [
    {
        // 1
        category: "Technical",
        question:
            "What is the general name of the company that publishes Blue Protocol?",
        choice: ["Square ENIX", "Bandai Namco", "Sega", "EA"],
        answer: ["Bandai Namco"],
    },
    {
        // 2
        category: "Technical",
        question:
            "What is the name of the development team responsible for Blue Protocol?",
        choice: [
            "Project Blue",
            "Project Blue Sky",
            "Bandai Namco",
            "Project Sky Blue",
        ],
        answer: ["Project Sky Blue"],
    },
    {
        // 3
        category: "Technical",
        question: "Who is the executive producer of Blue Protocol?",
        choice: [
            "Soukichi Shimooka",
            "Keisuke Fukuzaki",
            "Takahiro Suzuki",
            "Kazuto Kirigaya",
        ],
        answer: ["Takahiro Suzuki"],
    },
    {
        // 4
        category: "Class",
        question: "What was the 5th class added to the game?",
        choice: ["Aegis Fighter", "Twin Striker", "Heavy Smasher", "Spell Caster"],
        answer: ["Heavy Smasher"],
    },
    {
        // 5
        category: "Lore",
        question: "What is the name of the Aegis Fighter class instructor?",
        choice: ["Lily", "Korz", "Manuel", "Seila"],
        answer: ["Korz"],
    },
    {
        // 6
        category: "Lore",
        question: "What is the name of the Twin Striker class instructor?",
        choice: ["Manuel", "Lily", "Seila", "Korz"],
        answer: ["Manuel"],
    },
    {
        // 7
        category: "Lore",
        question: "What is the name of the Blast Archer class instructor?",
        choice: ["Korz", "Lily", "Manuel", "Seila"],
        answer: ["Lily"],
    },
    {
        // 8
        category: "Lore",
        question: "What is the name of the Spell Caster class instructor?",
        choice: ["Korz", "Manuel", "Seila", "Lily"],
        answer: ["Seila"],
    },
    {
        // 9
        category: "Class",
        question: "Perfection is an ability for which Twin Striker skill?",
        choice: ["Blood Axe", "Storm Rush", "Burning Rush", "Vortex Impact"],
        answer: ["Burning Rush"],
    },
    {
        // 10
        category: "Class",
        question: "What class uses the skill War Cry?",
        choice: ["Aegis Fighter", "Twin Striker", "Blast Archer", "Spell Caster"],
        answer: ["Twin Striker"],
    },
    {
        // 11
        category: "Class",
        question: "What class uses the skill Negative Resonance?",
        choice: ["Blast Archer", "Spell Caster", "Aegis Fighter", "Twin Striker"],
        answer: ["Blast Archer"],
    },
    {
        // 12
        category: "Class",
        question: "Acceleration is an ability for which Blast Archer skill?",
        choice: ["Charge Arrow", "Riesel Shower", "Hunter Spirit", "Arrow Rush"],
        answer: ["Riesel Shower"],
    },
    {
        // 13
        category: "Class",
        question: "Blast Archer’s backward + regular attack 1 key results in what?",
        choice: [
            "Healing Boost Buff",
            "Movement Speed Buff",
            "Attack Buff",
            "Attack Speed Buff",
        ],
        answer: ["Movement Speed Buff"],
    },
    {
        // 14
        category: "Class",
        question: "Which Spell Caster ability has the same name for two skills?",
        choice: ["Escalation", "Element Escalate", "EP Save", "Rapid Charge"],
        answer: ["Escalation"],
    },
    {
        // 15
        category: "Class",
        question: "Which class uses the skill Engram Charge?",
        choice: ["Aegis Fighter", "Spell Caster", "Twin Striker", "Blast Archer"],
        answer: ["Spell Caster"],
    },
    {
        // 16
        category: "Class",
        question: "Starlight is an ability for which Aegis Fighter skill?",
        choice: [
            "Regeneration",
            "Sunrise Charge",
            "Judgement Shield",
            "Celestial Pillar",
        ],
        answer: ["Celestial Pillar"],
    },
    {
        // 17
        category: "Story",
        question:
            "Which story character do you meet after defeating an Avalitia for the first time?",
        choice: ["Jake", "Einrain", "Merlouf", "Aerinse"],
        answer: ["Merlouf"],
    },
    {
        // 18
        category: "Story",
        question: "What is the name of the NPC that gives you a mount imajinn?",
        choice: ["Roger", "Dean", "Studs", "Quinn"],
        answer: ["Studs"],
    },
    {
        // 19
        category: "Story",
        question:
            "What is the name of the inn that you wake up in after meeting Feste for the first time?",
        choice: [
            "The Double-Faced Coin",
            "Black Masked Inn",
            "Hunter's Breeze",
            "The Highland Inn",
        ],
        answer: ["The Double-Faced Coin"],
    },
    {
        // 20
        category: "Story",
        question: "Who is the self-proclaimed “best of the best” adventurer?",
        choice: ["Einrain", "Jake", "Main Character", "Aerinse"],
        answer: ["Jake"],
    },
    {
        // 21
        category: "Story",
        question: "What is the name of the mysterious girl at the Bapharia Shrine?",
        choice: ["Aylin", "Sophia", "Einrain", "Aerinse"],
        answer: ["Einrain"],
    },
    {
        // 22
        category: "Story",
        question:
            "What are you, the player, referred to as by some characters in the story?",
        choice: ["Adventurer", "Visitor", "Traveler", "Leaper"],
        answer: ["Visitor"],
    },
    {
        // 23
        category: "Story",
        question: "What is Aenrinse’s bodyguard’s name?",
        choice: ["Jake", "Einrain", "Feste", "Tyris"],
        answer: ["Tyris"],
    },
    {
        // 24
        category: "Story",
        question:
            "What is the name of the NPC at Minsterhorn who tells you to go to the Pillar of Divinity?",
        choice: ["Jake", "Milene", "Merlouf", "Feste"],
        answer: ["Milene"],
    },
    {
        // 25
        category: "Story",
        question:
            "What is the name of the girl in charge of Adventurer Registration at the Frontiering Station?",
        choice: ["Milene", "Murrie", "Melrouf", "Einrain"], // Melrophe :/
        answer: ["Murrie"],
    },
    {
        // 26
        category: "Lore",
        question: "What’s the name of the  town that you start in?",
        choice: ["Bapharia ", "Asterleeds", "Salamzart", "Lapenta"],
        answer: ["Asterleeds"],
    },
    {
        // 27
        category: "Lore",
        question: "What is the desert-themed town called?",
        choice: ["Ul'dah", "Salamzart", "Death Valley", "Durango"],
        answer: ["Salamzart"],
    },
    {
        // 28
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "Which color liquid memory increases enemy drop rate?",
        choice: ["Yellow", "Red", "Purple", "Green"],
        answer: ["Purple"],
    },
    {
        // 29
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "What is the max amount of attachment slots a weapon can have?",
        choice: ["3", "6", "4", "5"],
        answer: ["4"],
    },
    {
        // 30
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "Which element has “high damage explosion” as a burst effect?",
        choice: ["Light", "Dark", "Ice", "Earth"],
        answer: ["Light"],
    },
    {
        // 31
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "How many waves does Arena [S Rank] have?",
        choice: ["30", "100", "25", "70"],
        answer: ["25"],
    },
    {
        // 32
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "What is the name for the highest level dungeon difficulty?",
        choice: [
            "Final Survey",
            "Ultra Survey",
            "Additional Survey",
            "Advanced Survey",
        ],
        answer: ["Advanced Survey"],
    },
    {
        // 33
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "What is the name of the boss in Valley of Machines?",
        choice: ["Quad Arm", "Reanimated Terror", "Ancient Android", "Demon Bhor"],
        answer: ["Quad Arm"],
    },
    {
        // 34
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "What zone is the town Larpal in?",
        choice: ["Asterleeds", "Fiel Pond", "Andra Basin", "Divine Haven Hill"],
        answer: ["Divine Haven Hill"],
    },
    {
        // 35
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "What is the first zone outside of Asterleeds called?",
        choice: [
            "Divine Haven Hill",
            "Skyquake Fields",
            "Andra Basin",
            "Soundless Foothills",
        ],
        answer: ["Skyquake Fields"],
    },
    {
        // 36
        category: "Gameplay",
        question:
            "What zone is the dungeon Dragon Claw Valley [Free Exploration] found in?",
        choice: ["Salamzart", "Minster Hills", "Skyquake fields", "Fiel Pond"],
        answer: ["Minster Hills"],
    },
    {
        // 37
        category: "Lore",
        question: "What is the world of BLUE PROTOCOL called?",
        choice: ["Asteria", "Bahamar", "Regnus", "Prectus"],
        answer: ["Regnus"],
    },
    {
        // 38
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "How many warp portals are in Asterleeds?",
        choice: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        answer: ["9"],
    },
    {
        // 39
        category: "Class",
        question: "Which class has the highest base attack on their weapons?",
        choice: ["Heavy Smasher", "Aegis Fighter", "Spell Caster", "Twin Striker"],
        answer: ["Twin Striker"],
    },
    {
        // 40
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "What is the default amount of stamina?",
        choice: ["200", "100", "150", "70"],
        answer: ["100"],
    },
    {
        // 41
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "How often do most elite monsters spawn?",
        choice: ["15 minutes", "10 minutes", "7 minutes", "30 minutes"],
        answer: ["15 minutes"],
    },
    {
        // 42
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "What is the name of the level 18 raid boss?",
        choice: ["Fiel", "Demidragon", "Undead Prince", "Hydra"],
        answer: ["Demidragon"],
    },
    {
        // 43
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "What is the max party size?",
        choice: ["3", "5", "6", "4"],
        answer: ["6"],
    },
    {
        // 44
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "How many players can be in a raid?",
        choice: ["15", "30", "40", "20"],
        answer: ["20"],
    },
    {
        // 45
        category: "Class",
        question: "Which class can equip the weapon Bapharia's Guidance?",
        choice: ["Blast Archer", "Aegis Fighter", "Spell caster", "Twin Striker"],
        answer: ["Aegis Fighter"],
    },
    {
        // 46
        category: "Class",
        question: "Which class has no heal skills?",
        choice: ["Twin Striker", "Spell Caster", "Aegis Fighter", "Blast Archer"],
        answer: ["Spell Caster"],
    },
    {
        // 47
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "What is the strongest battle imajinn called?",
        choice: ["Sealed Tyranny", "Eternal Rage", "Red Splash", "Iron Fangs"],
        answer: ["Sealed Tyranny"],
    },
    {
        // 48
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "How many healer-type battle imajinn are there?",
        choice: ["4", "2", "8", "3"],
        answer: ["3"],
    },
    {
        // 49
        category: "Technical",
        question: "What year did the development of BLUE PROTOCOL begin?",
        choice: ["2014", "2016", "2020", "2021"],
        answer: ["2014"],
    },
    {
        // 50
        category: "Gameplay",
        question:
            "How many character voice options can you choose from during character creation?",
        choice: ["7", "1", "5", "3"],
        answer: ["3"],
    },
    {
        // 51
        category: "Class",
        question: "Which class is often considered the biggest support role?",
        choice: ["Spell Caster", "Blast Archer", "Twin Striker", "Aegis fighter"],
        answer: ["Blast Archer"],
    },
    {
        // 52
        category: "Gameplay",
        question:
            "How many Permanent Skills & Tactical Abilities are the same for each class?",
        choice: ["17", "13", "14", "15"],
        answer: ["14"],
    },
    {
        // 53
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "How many different inner imajinn slots are there?",
        choice: ["5", "3", "6", "8"],
        answer: ["5"],
    },
    {
        // 54
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "How many accessory slots are confirmed by the developers?",
        choice: ["5", "8", "7", "10"],
        answer: ["7"],
    },
    {
        // 55
        category: "Gameplay",
        question: "How much stamina does evasion consume?",
        choice: ["20", "25", "15", "30"],
        answer: ["25"],
    },
];

export default TRIVIA;